<?xml version="1.0" encoding="Big5"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="blogdisplay.xsl"?>
<blog>
	<title>Personal Blog using XML technology</title>
	<author>Jeffrey Garcia</author>
	<country>Hong Kong</country>
	<company>University of South Australia</company>
	<year>2006</year>
	<shortdescription>ECT Assignment 1</shortdescription>

	<post>
		<postrating>1</postrating>
		<posttitle>Java EE 5 SDK and Sun Java System Application Server Platform Edition 9</posttitle>
		<postbody>
			Sun Microsystems released Sun Java System Application 
			Server Platform Edition 9 (hereinafter called Application Server PE 9), 
			which implements the latest technologies of the Java Platform, Enterprise 
			Edition 5 (Java EE 5) Specification, and offers many new features targeted 
			at improving developer productivity. This free release is based on the source 
			code developed by Sun engineers and the GlassFish community (an open-source 
			community that is developing a Java EE 5 application server). 
			
			Application Server PE 9 is included as part of the Java EE 5 SDK—an all-in-one 
			bundle with which developers can quickly learn, develop, and deploy new 
			enterprise Java technologies. (More than 5 million developers have downloaded 
			earlier versions of Java EE SDK.)
		</postbody>
		<postdate>28/July/2006</postdate>
		<comments>
			<comment>
				<commentbody>
					With a primary focus on ease of development, the Java EE 
					5 platform offers developers ready access to a secure, 
					portable, and scalable platform for their enterprise 
					applications. Java EE 5 technology makes coding simpler 
					and more straightforward. How? Through the use of Java 
					annotations, programming based on POJO (Plain Old Java Object), 
					and resource injection concepts. 
				</commentbody>
				<commentauthor>Tony Ng</commentauthor>
				<commentdate>2/August/2006</commentdate>
			</comment>
			<comment>
				<commentbody>
					Java annotations can now be used to specify the mapping of Java 
					business objects to a relational database. The persistence 
					implementation in the application server supports both the 
					generation of database schemas from Java objects and the 
					mapping of existing database schemas to Java objects. In 
					addition to using persistence inside the EJB container, 
					you can use the Persistence API directly with Java Standard 
					Edition. This allows maximum flexibility in your persistence 
					needs, with a common solution for both client and server 
					environments.
				</commentbody>
				<commentauthor>Jerome</commentauthor>
				<commentdate>3/August/2006</commentdate>
			</comment>
		</comments>
	</post>

	<post>
		<postrating>2</postrating>
		<posttitle>Download Internet Explorer 7 Beta 3 (Easier to use, more secure)</posttitle>
		<postbody>
			Internet Explorer 7 Beta 3 is now available for download and includes 
			improvements in reliability, compatibility, user features, and security. 
			Although Internet Explorer 7 Beta 2 was layout complete, based on  
			end users's feedback, Microsoft made some additional changes to the look and 
			feel of the browser. Beta 3 allows users to add the e-mail button back 
			to the toolbar, enables users to reorder the tabs by dragging them to the 
			left or right, and enables horizontal scrolling while zooming.
		</postbody>
		<postdate>15/July/2006</postdate>
		<comments>
			<comment>
				<commentbody>
					To improve the RSS experience, Internet Explorer 7 
					now allows users to update all their RSS feeds automatically. 
					In addition, the user has more control in marking their RSS 
					feeds as "READ."
				</commentbody>
				<commentauthor>RK</commentauthor>
				<commentdate>27/July/2006</commentdate>
			</comment>
		</comments>
	</post>

	<post>
		<postrating>1</postrating>
		<posttitle>Google 要提供詐欺點閱數字給廣告主</posttitle>
		<postbody>
			為了回應線上廣告產業對於點閱詐欺的憂慮，Google決定在AdWord廣告機制中，
			提供無效點閱數字供廣告主參考。 

			Google信賴安全商業產品經理 Shuman Ghosemajumder 表示，現在廣告主將可看
			得到Google 所找出的無效點閱數，以及整個比率的多寡等統計數字。 

			點閱詐欺廣告的發生通常是內容出版者自己點自家網站的廣告來衝營收，或者廠
			商刻意點選對手的廣告來吃掉對方的廣告預算。Ghosemajumder 表示，Google 
			不會收取無效點閱的費用。
		</postbody>
		<postdate>1/July/2006</postdate>
		<comments>
			<comment>
				<commentbody>
					在新系統下，AdWords客戶可看到每天無效點閱的數字，
					且可回溯至今年年初。Ghosemajumder 表示，Google 
					無法將所有資料都提供給客戶看，不然有心人士可透
					過反向工程破解Google的運作方式。
				</commentbody>
				<commentauthor>陳仔</commentauthor>
				<commentdate>2/July/2006</commentdate>
			</comment>
		</comments>
	</post>
</blog>